theistudio.com 2019-04-12

# Privacy | WordPress Consultant: Judith Kallos | At Your Service...

## The IStudio® and Your Privacy

This privacy notice discloses the privacy practices for The IStudio®. This privacy notice applies solely to information collected by this website. This page will notify you of the following:

  * What personally identifiable information is collected from you through my website, how it is used and with whom it may be shared.
  * What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data.
  * The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information.
  * How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.

### Information Collection, Use, and Sharing

I am the sole owner of this website. Only I have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give me via e-mail or other direct contact from you. I will not expose, sell or rent this information to anyone – ever!

I will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted me. This includes subscribing to my WPMuse Briefings. I will not share your information with any third party outside of my organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request(s).

If we do business together, I have no visibility or access to your payment information. That is stored and secured by PayPal, my payment processor.

Unless you ask me not to, I may contact you via email in the future to tell you about important developments, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy.

### Your Access to and Control Over Information

You may opt out of any future contacts from me at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting me via the e-mail address or phone number given on my website:

  * See what data I have about you, if any.
  * Change/correct any data I have about you.
  * Have me delete any data I have about you.
  * Express any concern you have about my use of your data.

### Security

I take precautions to protect your information. You will notice that that my site is secured (https) and the green padlock is in the locked position in you browser’s location bar. When you submit sensitive information via my website, your information is protected both online and offline.

All information is encrypted and transmitted to me in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a closed lock icon in your Web browser, or looking for “https” at the beginning of the address of all pages on my website.

While I use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, I also protect your information off line. I am the only person with access to your information. The computers/servers in which I store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment and are password protected.

### Cookies & Miscellany

> When someone visits TheIStudio.com, I use a third party service, Google Analytics, to collect standard information and details in regard to my visitor’s behavior patterns. I do this to find out things such as the number of visitors to the various pages and areas of my website. This information is only processed in a way which does not personally identify any visitor. I, nor Google, makes any attempt to find out the identities of those visiting our website without their knowledge. 

I use “cookies” on this site. A cookie is a piece of data stored on a site visitor’s hard drive to help me improve your access to my site and identify repeat visitors to my site. Cookies can also enable me to track and target the interests of my users to enhance their experience on my site. Usage of cookies is in **no way** linked to any personally identifiable information.

This website contains links to other sites. Please be aware that I am not responsible for the content or privacy practices of these other sites. I encourage my users to be aware when they leave my site and to read the privacy statements of any other site that collects personally identifiable information.

If you have any difficulties or questions about The IStudio®‘s privacy policy, please [contact me](https://www.theistudio.com/contact/).
